Umpires are ready. Fielders are ready
setting up the field. Evdas the captain
and we are all in readiness to start.
Okay, so here we go
in the countdown of five
4 3 2 1 game on.
Post ball. A bit of misfield there at
square leg. Will they come back for two?
And they'll get it easily.
Just swiping it [music] towards that
square leg and two runs taken.
So I welcome all the viewers and
spectators watching us live. I welcome
you all.
It's a great environment here at Fatima
grounds vidya Mumbai.
Good placement
for a single.
It's a bright sunny day. Weather is
clear. Perfect condition to play. and
quarterfinal one already started.
That's a lefty righty combination.
And now captain Vishal Jada on strike
for him. One fielder at square leg and
one at Longon.
Wow, we have the IPL wipes also on
three for no loss after two balls being
bowled.
No ball signal by the umpire.
And we'll be free hit coming up.
And this time looking to connect for big
one. Missed it completely. Good bowling
from Mahes Shetty. Started the
proceedings.
Excellent bowling. Excellent bowling.
putting pressure on Captain Vishal.
We'll get a single
and softly played with single run at
covers.
So steady start from team Howen. Good
bowling from Mahesh Shetty. One has gone
six for no loss. team out.
the captain Dave Das into the attack.
Ashish on strike.
106 for no loss.
That's very good bowling into the block
hole. Just a single. They're not
allowing batter to play for the big
shots.
Now they the lefty righty combination
and they will burn the calories of the
fielders.
Vishal Jada one of the strongest
contender
looking to connect but going down the
leg side and they're going for one more
run. J it could be the chance at the
non- striker end
and two extra added in the total nine
for no loss.
So back-to-back wides 10 for no loss.
The score is going that double digit.
Wow. Good stop in the follow through by
skipper Das.
The score remains 10 for no loss.
Oh, that's outside edge and gone.
The much needed breakthrough and captain
strikes.
Excellent taken at caught behind by the
wicket keeper Kush.
The new batter Matesh Patil come coming
at number three.
It's down the leg side for wide Mr. Home
Singh signaling that wide
1.31 for one the score
once again going down the leg side
need to uh with some some strong
strategy.
Many wides in this over so far.
Four wides so far in this over.
Excellent bowling. That's very good
comeback. Yes. No. Yes. No. And there's
something mixed up between the batters.
But finally
they managed to take a single
with the single 13 for one.
Change in the field settings.
Long on and between mid wicket and
square leg.
Just going again outside the off line
for wide. Many extras coming
already. They have seven extras.
They got He got a wicket, but many runs
also coming for the batting side.
Looking for a big one.
He's got that outside edge,
but there's a feeder at short third man
for a single.
So 15 for one last ball coming up of the
second What?
Oh, that's a very good boiling. Wow.
That's a very good comeback
and end of the over. Two was gone. 15
for one. Howen
So two was gone 15 for one. Once again,
good morning and welcome to the ICA
Lombard presenting Brokers Premier
League 2026
season 3
and this is quarterfinal one in progress
as a team Hen taking up with Unilite
Strikers.
Initially Unilite strikers won the toss
elected to field first. They invited
team Hen to bat first. So that's end of
the power play. Many fielders can be go
outside a circle but minimum four
fielders should be inside a circle.
Starting the new over
captain Vishal Jadawan strike
and that's a good strike that's gone
high in the air.
Oh, he's dropped it. Mahesh was the
fielder at Longon. He drops it and
Vishal Jada survives.
This is the pressure of the cordifel
game. It's not easy to take that high
catch.
That bit troubles a lot after you
dropping that catch and you have
immediately a change in the field
settings because lefty right combination
on the crease.
No balls by the empire.
So no plus
two runs.
Team Hen need to come with some strong
strategy. Many runs are considered in
extras, some in no balls.
The score is 19 for one after 2.1
and that's a good strike high in the air
but it will land safe.
only a single
241 with that single 2.2
And they know the importance of the
game, the field settings.
The team who wins will get semi-final
ticket.
And for the leftander long, we have the
fielder at
almost at cow corner
and one at square leg.
It's going wide once again. Back to
back. They're getting more extras.
They almost conceded nine extras.
21 for one.
Dead ball.
Looking for that maning wicket
again down the leg side for wide
22 for and seven runs in this over so
far. Two balls being bowled.
Rahul Bahiti
last night hero he was in the last over
defended the score won by six runs.
What a match that was against
Gallagher United. One ball seven needed
and defended very well. And this time
high in the air will land safe.
But there was a backup fielder and two
runs taken. Good cricket from the team
Hen
24 for one after 2.4 Four
is
checkarash
or battery char.
That's the first boundary of the innings
from Vishal Jadu
and that's high in the air
and again he has dropped that catch
couldn't get hold of it once again
batsman survive Vishal Jado
so three gone 30 for one team Houden
Te
quarterfinal
cricket
Sunday cricket
90s kid all will relate
bowling mah shetty
Mesh Parish
strategy set
Two runs make
two
3.3 33 for one. Howen.
Vishad field setting on site.
Safe.
Only a single.
>> [music]
>> extemp.
And the strikes second wicket fall 3.5
34 for
New batter Amit Anik Gerkar on strike.
Last ball before
a good defense, good bowling.
So successful over comes to an end and
Maheshi two over 8 for one. Just four
runs of the door and one wicket. Four
was gone 34 for two. Henik4
team
strong of his left side region.
Char overies though four was gone. 34
for two
oras
strikers
come
Back to back. Two wickets.
Catch running catch or
chis.
How done?
Nala Siddan Gad Striker.
Better in bowling.
is over.
Longish
long off.
Bin bowling.
Stop.
Back up back.
Settling
weather is bowling. Should the icon
Totally beat
batsman.
Bad news.
Fielding teams
better
charis. Spectine.
about 43 for three. Six was gone. 43 for
three. Howen.
91.
That's well driven into the covers, but
it was straight to the fieldder.
Tanayana the fielder at covers only a
single
Javalis Piniel
in deep a deep square leg and deep
cover. Long off, long on. And they have
mid wicket.
Just tucks it away for a single.
45 for three.
And that's a good strike.
Only a single. They're looking for two.
46 for three. Good over so far. Just
three runs. Back to back. Three singles.
Back to back four singles. Good ball
from Das.
47 for three.
Last two balls coming up of the seventh
over.
Will they go for some big hits? Need
some fireworks here.
That's high in the air
and dropped it. Many catches dropped.
Almost four catches dropped today in the
fielding side
and the batsman survives.
It's not [music] easy to take that
catch.
single run.
So, five singles of the over so far.
Last ball coming up. 48 for three.
This time going much wide outside the
off line for wide. 49 for three. With it
wide.
Last ball of the penalty mate over.
49 for three.
Swing and a miss. Good bowling. End of
the over. Seven gone. Howen 49 for
three. Sawad unaspin Howen.
So coming up the last over of the first
innings you're watching IC Lombard
proudly presenting Brokers Premier
League 2025 2026 [music]
season 3
49 for three.
Last five balls
in bowling.
Matraana
1.2 overs.
Last four balls coming up of the first
innings.
This time [music] trying to bowl very
much short of pitch length. Lost his
momentum completely or Howen Pasan Bur
50 for team Hen
with it wide. 50 for three. Last four
balls.
Yes. Outside edge and gone. That's a
fourth wicket down
7.350 for four.
Tanayana very good bowling something to
cheer for him because he's restrict
the team Howen they expecting 60 70
maybe but that's a good comeback from
the team unilite strikers
Last three balls coming up. Vishal the
new batter
fulls ball.
Will they come back for two? They're
running. They're going and direct hit.
And yes, that's out. Direct hit and
gone.
One more wicket fall. 51 for five round
team.
That's a very good throw from the
fieldder.
So that's a good throw from Mad.
51 for five. 7.4. Last two balls coming
up of the first innings. Quarterfinal
one is on.
The team who wins will directly go into
the semi-finals.
Karthik Kohli.
A new batter
get extra run added to the total 52 for
five.
again a wide
17 extras in the innings
53 for five. Last two balls
fulls ball and that's got good strike
towards mid wicket and they're going for
two runs. This could be one more chance
for them out and Tanmay not collected
that ball. Two runs 55 for five. Last
ball coming up of the first innings.
Let's see. The ball is going towards
that final leg region. Will it run away?
Yes. Four runs finished off in style.
And that's the end of the first innings
after eight overs. 59 for five.
initially won the toss by unilite
strikers decided to bowl first. They
invited team Hen to bat first and eight
was gone 59 for five. The target to
chase will be 60.
Get to watch ICI Lombard presents
Brokers Premier League 2026 season 3.
And now heading towards the quarterfinal
2 time. And may I request Pink Panthers,
Pink Warriors
and Anandraati United.
We are fan of Pink Panthers. Pink
Warriors. Pink Warriors captain and
Anandraati United.
So my request captain of pink warriors
and captain of Anandraati headed.
I request team Anandraati captain
Anandraati United
Pink Warriors captain
Pink Panther's captain for the coin toss
Come on team unil strikers batters a
Okay. Hello and welcome back. Good
morning once again to the exciting game
of cricket. This is the quarterfinal one
of ICS Lumbar present brokers league
2026. Here we go. First ball is
batted first [music] eight over 59 for
five.
Rahul Bayi
Man,
I Hat.
The equation says 36 balls and 53 runs.
So good uh start at the day two of ICS
Lombard Brokers Premier League 2026
season 3.
We had a first day very exciting 16
teams participated
in this tournament and now eight teams
going for that semi-final glory for the
final glory and who will that semi
semi-final the four teams
after this match coming up the
quarterfinal two pink panthers
Anandraati united
The third quarterfinal will be edit
titans one team and fourth will be
prudent warriors and a aon.
Lot of excitement coming up Sunday
special Sunday
interesting match but is over.
L
9 for one
over Norati over
K now Target
running.
Smart cricket.
Back to back. Two runs.
11 for one.
sir Rahul Dubai retired
and the new batter
may shy on strike.
Three gone 18 for two.
Let's see. Only a single run.
They're looking for two runs, but very
good fielding.
It's a long fielder coming towards that
30 yard circle.
So 19 for three
and the skipper
Coming at number five,
the entry is made like MS Dhoni is on
strike.
2011 World Cup final
and tucks it away nicely
and they'll go for two runs.
What a match 2011 World Cup final. Gamir
played 97 runs and Dhoni middle order
performed really well.
And India got the second World Cup win
after 1983.
Excellent batting from Devdas. Very good
start. First ball two runs then single
run.
The team under pressure and captain
walks in.
38 runs and 26 balls. The equation artis
or chub is gained
over
this match.
Strikers
25 balls and 36 runs.
Last ball of this over.
We'll get only single.
And Mad Kadam is batting really well.
35 runs in 24 balls.
So four overs going 25 for three United
strikers and they need 35 runs in next
four overs.
You're watching ICIC Lombard presents
Brokers Premier League 2026 season 3.
And let's see now Anik Kerkar the new
bowler into the attack
short man Prias.
This could be the chance for the catch.
Oh, very good balling. Oh, chance. Could
be the chance of that run out behind his
thumbs.
But keeper is not taking that risk for
that extra runs.
Good bowling from Anikit.
That's going uh backward region. Maybe
we'll wait for the umpire signal
that came from the bat.
two runs,
32 runs in 21 balls. Now the equation
says for unilite strikers
but run a key game 21 balls.
Team Houden will go for
this partnership to be broken because
the two big contenders Dvdas and Madok
Kadam.
Oh, good bowling.
That's what uh the bowler will and
that's a leg bic umpire raising
bowling at uh the line of the l middle
of the line
and that's
29 from 18 balls and this will be the
interesting over coming up
that two interesting overs from the
team.
Strikers target
29 runs in 18 balls.
Excellent fielding only a single and
that's what captain Vishal is expecting.
Effective efficient fieldings.
Please run.
That could be taken.
Excellent shot inside out. One bounce
into the fence for four runs. A much
needed boundary for the team Uniline
Strikers.
What a shot that was from
Madok Kadam. He's batting really well.
23 of 15 with two fours.
Just a single match is getting more
interesting here.
They're batting really well. They're
fielding really well. That's end of the
overadalis.
That six was gone. 39 for three.
21 runs.
21 runs in 12 balls.
can get 10 runs, 11 runs.
They will go for two. They're going for
two runs. That's good running.
The fielder at short mid wicket not able
to stop that ball.
And the equation says
18 runs in 10 balls.
What a match.
This could a chance for the run out and
throw was not dead fine.
Single run.
17 runs, nine balls. What a match
down the track playing it toward covers.
They're going for two runs and this
could be the chance for the run out. Oh,
the keeper has not collected that ball
in his hand
and look at the disappointment on their
face.
What a match. Vishal is not happy at
all.
Two runs taken 15 runs from eight balls.
15 runs, eight balls. Important two
balls coming up.
Very good bowling.
Anik at his best.
They need one more dot ball to get that
15 runs in last over.
And this time, good strike. Will they
come back for two?
>> They're going for it.
And they'll get two runs.
So that's end of the over number seven.
47 for three
or up cricket
will which team will qualify in the
semiinal one howen or unilite striker
let's
And wow, THAT'S GONE HIGH IN THE AIR FOR
SIX RUNS. [screaming]
A MUCH NEEDED MAXIMUM hit from Madok
Kadam.
And with that, the equation says they
need one more big hit to get the ticket
into this semi-final.
What a body from Madam
Char.
Tension rising both the teams.
I'm holding my nerves in the com box.
3521 two four and 1 six. This is like a
match winning batting from Madukadam.
Here we go. Charbal chiran.
Oh, HE'S GONE. WHAT IS THIS HAPPENING?
THEY GOT A FINAL ONE. THAT'S A VERY good
throw and excellent batting.
A good. Can we have a big round of
applause to Mad Kadam?
Excellent batting. 3522. Two fours and
one maximum hit. Or
run.
Six runs and three balls.
What a match.
DJ
Heartbeat sound effect.
That's a heartbeat.
What a match. What a match. First
quarterfinal
of ICA Lombard Brokers Premier League
2026 season 3.
Akshai Pande the new batter.
Thank you DJ.
Here we go.
And this time hit hard. Very good stop.
They're going for TWO RUNS. AND THIS
COULD BE ONE MORE WICKET FALL.
One hit, one big hit and that's it. A
team Hen will go for that wicket
better match Sunday funday.
Kosh Shaha the new batter walks in
Paran
outside edge
only a single. They're going for one
more run. This will be the suicidal run
out for sure. One more wicket. And they
need four runs. Paul or Jaran.
What a match. What a match.
Egg ball charon.
Here
we go.
One ball, four runs.
and that's a good strike.
Oh, very good stop.
At least they GO FOR THREE RUNS. THEY'RE
GOING FOR THREE RUN. THIS COULD BE THE
CHANCE. [screaming] AND THE MATCH TEAM
HOUDEN THEY GOT THE VICTORY. WHAT A
MATCH. [screaming] THE FIRST
QUARTERFINAL ENDED IN DRAMATIC CINEMATIC
FANTASTIC.
WOW.
one by